[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 18]
The secret of immortality has been revealed.
The 3,000-year-old immortal body has been completely exposed.
The story is blowing up online.
It turns out someone who's lived for 3,000 years
really does exist.
What are they doing?
Chasing the hype.
They're just chasing the hype.
Let's go. Hurry, hurry.
What should we do now?
It seems that time has come again.
Time...
time for what?
Time to move.
I'll do it.
Done.
[Step 1: Find the whistleblower]
Step one of crisis management.
Find the source of the leak.
Buy out the news.
And cut off the spread first.
Your account is the first source.
Tell me where the information came from.
You won't be shortchanged.
Someone gave me some materials.
They said I could make a lot of money if I exposed it.
Let me
see your sincerity.
Everything that person gave me is here.
Step two.
Fight fire with fire.
It's easier to make people feel like they've been played
[Step 2: Fight fire with fire]
than to make them believe you.
Of course, it's our anti-aging cream.
Guys, our anti-aging cream
absorbs super fast.
Keep using it can fade fine lines.
It's truly a miracle for keeping you looking young.
Click the link in the top left corner.
You can also get a 99-yuan coupon.
Say it.
Price.
Not 1999.
What? Only...
Only 199.
-It's so expensive. -It's a good deal.
No, no.
Hello, hello.
The brand just said
they can give us another 50% off.
Oh my god, look.
The secret to eternal life is being livestreamed,
and they even have a shopping cart.
The comments all say this person is a scammer.
Waited two days for nothing.
Just another clout chaser.
Let's go, everyone.
Forget it. It's really boring. Let's go.
I thought there was big news. Waited for nothing.
Let's go.
Step three.
[Step 3: Find the mastermind]
Find the person behind this.
This leak is too precise.
Someone must be deliberately targeting us.
He actually has evidence
that we have lived for 3,000 years.
What does he stand to gain
by spreading all this evidence?
Boss.
Are you sure all these things need to be moved?
yes.
Move them.
Princess Ningjia.
Song Baiwei.
Wait.
General Yu.
I didn't expect that in this life,
the one Princess Ningjia fell in love with
would be you.
I remembered something very important.
I think I need to tell you.
Your clothes...
A disguise.
Couple outfits.
Let's get down to business.
Okay.
I remembered something.
The person who killed me in the Republic of China era
said something to me before I died.
He said, "General Yu,
I didn't expect
the person Princess Ningjia fell in love with in this life
would be you."
Who do you think he is?
How could he know our identities from 3,000 years ago
and live until the Republic of China era?
Wait a minute.
You mean
the person who killed you in the Republic of China era
knew our identities in Southern Qin?
Could it be
that besides you and me in this world,
there is a third immortal?
Maybe more than three.
The person who leaked the news
knew we've been in love for 3,000 years.
Maybe he is also an immortal.
There's no such coincidence.
Maybe the person who killed you that night
is the same person
who leaked the news.
If that's true,
for so many years,
he has been secretly tracking our whereabouts,
but we know nothing about him.
If it's about immortality,
you can ask Yu Tu.
After all, she knows the most about it.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Are you still feeling unwell?
I feel dizzy.
Why are you so hot?
Do you have a fever?
Let me take you to the hospital first.
Thanks, baby.
Don't worry.
[Blood Collection Hall]
Fill this out, right?
Number 51.
Number 52.
Are you scared?
Are you kidding?
I'm not even afraid of death.
Why would I be afraid of this?
Really?
It's your turn.
Clench your fist.
Number 53.
I'm fine now.
Let's go back and help Qiu find clues.
No way.
I made a promise to Song Yiqiu,
and I must keep it.
You run an art gallery. You're not a cop.
Why do you care so much?
I'm sorry.
My friend is a little afraid
of needles.
No, I'm not.
Come on.
Go away. Go away.
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid.
What?
So there really are more immortals
in this world than just my uncle and Ms. Song.
Of course.
Did you think my sister and I were the only two demons?
Exactly.
Aren't you?
The reasons for immortality in this world
mostly stem from obsession.
Extreme love or hate
can make time stop.
He killed people in the Republic of China era,
and now he's secretly using tricks
to surround our house.
He doesn't sound like a good person.
I don't even want to think
about what he'll do next.
No.
Ning Changyue and I
can get hurt and sick now.
So,
we could die at any time.
Before that,
I must catch that scumbag.
Don't tell Song Yiqiu
about what happened today.
What?
You mean
your phobia of needles?
I'm not afraid.
I won't tell her.
Don't tell her.
Oh my god.
This...
What's wrong?
Is it serious?
Am I going to die?
Look at you.
No, no, no.
I'm just kidding.
The doctor said
you just have a slight cold.
You'll be fine after taking some medicine.
Seriously, you.
I wonder how Song Yiqiu
is doing now.
My old lady,
be good.
When you get better,
I'll cook whatever you want to eat.
Okay, okay.
Are you happy?
Be good.
Okay.
Lin Huai.
If
you were going to die tomorrow,
would you be afraid?
Die tomorrow?
Of course I'd be afraid.
Have you ever heard
that before people die,
their whole life
flashes before their eyes?
What I fear most is
waiting until next time to say what I want to say,
and waiting until next time to do what I want to do.
But if I die tomorrow,
there will be no next time.
That's what I fear most.
I have to go back and help Qiu.
These photos and notes
are our clues.
Find the people from each era
who could have contacted them.
The mastermind must be among them.
From the unofficial records of Southern Qin,
to the alumni directory of the Republic of China,
not a single one can be missing,
♪ You said you were content to linger in the space between ♪
♪ Unwilling to cross the line you drew for me yourself ♪
♪ But in the end ♪
♪ One foot of yours still steps across the line ♪
♪ While the other remains on the other side ♪
♪ Keeping me shut out ♪
♪ And now all that's left is me ♪
♪ With nothing but this dizziness as the ending ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I thought I could hold on for another day ♪
♪ Hoping to find the part of you that still wants to save me ♪
♪ I once thought I was strong enough to endure ♪
♪ I should have known all along that you would be the one to break me ♪
I got it.
Come here, quick.
Coming.
What did you find out?
You two write this sentence down.
This is what I wrote.
Can you see the difference?
[They have been in love for 3,000 years]
Mine is uglier?
There's one extra stroke
in "love" compared to mine.
But I wrote it the same way.
Wh-wh-wh-
What does it mean?
This is a unique writing style of the Southern Qin royal family.
Legend has it
that the mother of the late Emperor of Southern Qin
had the character "love" in her given name.
According to tradition,
one stroke should be omitted when writing it
to observe the naming taboo.
But the late Emperor believed
that omitting a stroke would lose its original meaning.
So he decreed
that all royal children and palace officials,
when writing the character. "love",
must add an extra stroke
to manifest its meaning.
What does
this mean?
The person who's been working against us all this time
is from the Southern Qin royal family.
How is it going?
Any progress?
Do you want something to eat?
This is...
The scope is now
narrowed down to the Southern Qin royal family.
But the Southern Qin royal family
has thousands of members.
So we have to check them one by one,
look into their backgrounds,
and rule them out one at a time.
These jade pendants...
Why do they look so familiar?
I think I saw one on the person
who killed me back then.
But the pattern was a bit different.
Draw it.
Okay.
It looked like this.
A snake shape.
I've seen this token before.
The snake pattern
is used by the Chief Eunuch.
Could it be him?
We've been looking in the wrong direction.
In the palace,
the people subject to the taboo weren't just members of the imperial family,
but also the palace servants.
The one who could access the core secret of immortality
and become obsessed with it
is the Emperor's chief eunuch,
Liu Yi.
He was the one who caught Yu Tu to take his blood.
He was also the one who injured you.
Your Highness.
You know what to do now, right?
He was the one who locked me in Duansi Palace,
and forced me to marry.
Impossible.
He couldn't have lived until now.
Unless
he used some dark magic.
No wonder.
He knows we can't die,
and ordinary assassinations are meaningless.
So he presumptuously killed Lin Huai
to find ways to torture you.
I see.
He is in the shadows,
and we are out in the open.
It's been 3,000 years.
It's time to settle our grudge.
[Survivor of General Yu's Rebellion, Southern Qin]
Here are all the men
who've shown up around the areas you and Ms. Song frequent
over the past six months
and look somewhat like
the photo she reconstructed.
Manager Qing Yuan.
Mr. Ning,
what brings you here?
Why didn't you have your assistant notify me in advance
so I could greet you at the door?
Are you looking for a new direction for your collection today?
Not exactly a direction.
Your auction house
handles a lot of items, right?
I'd like you to help me check
if you've ever seen an identity token of this style.
This identity token
has strong Southern Qin characteristics.
This is indeed an item from Southern Qin.
The owner of this identity token
is my old friend.
Finding it
might lead to news about him.
So I hope you can keep an eye out.
Whether on the market or through private channels,
if you see anything with a similar pattern,
please notify me immediately.
I have a friend
who happens to be an expert in Southern Qin artifacts.
How about
I contact them for you?
That's great.
Please contact them for me right away.
I'll head over right now.
Okay.
I was recommended by Manager Qing Yuan.
This is a unique writing style of the Southern Qin royal family.
that all royal children and palace officials,
when writing the character. "love",
must add an extra stroke
to emphasize its meaning.
Qing Yuan.
Where is Qing Yuan?
She just left.
Today is her last day at work.
[Longevity and Love Lidded Jar, Southern Qin]
Manager Qing Yuan.
I brought you some fruit.
Long time no see,
Princess Ningjia.